picreel.com 2015-04-13

# Privacy Policy | Picreel.com

## Privacy Policy

Picreel Privacy Policy

Picreel sets this Privacy Policy to inform you, our visitor on how we utilize personal information that we gathered from you. We respect the privacy of our visitors so we will protect your personal information which you shared to us. Personal information gathered will only be useful in filling orders. Disclosure of visitor’s personal information on this site is prohibited.

Use of Collected Information

  * Just like any other site; we only collect vital information upon registration, placing orders or filling out an order form. Personal information that we ask for the following: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information and the like.
  * Picreel’s goal in gathering information is to respond to your individual needs in the most possible and easiest way, in the shortest possible time. In our aim to serve you best, we would be happy to receive feedbacks from you and these feedbacks you share will help in improving our website and our services.
  * As our client, we want to pass on the best customer service and support a company could offer. Words from you will help us continuously grow in responding to our client’s needs.
  * Picreel aims to have a long and harmonious relationship with its clients, with this objective, we believe that having clear and fast communication will make dealings easier and faster. Your personal information will play a big role in this aspect.
  * Different security measures are being applied to ensure the safety of your personal information which you entrusted to us.
  * Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology is a secure server which we use to keep all supplied sensitive personal information, bank and credit card details, among others. These sensitive details are only accessible to very few individuals who have special access to the system.

Use of Cookies

Picreel utilizes the function of cookies for the purpose of, but not limited to, recognizing your browser, recalling certain information, saving your preferences for future visit and/or disclosing for the purpose of internal transaction within the company’s authorized staff.Turning off your cookies can be an option or you may set your computer to alert you when cookies are having its way, however, some of our services may not work as expected in the absence of these cookies. As an alternative, you can reach us through our customer service.

Disclosure of Collected Information

Because your security is our primary concern, personal information are not sold, traded or transferred to others unless they are trusted third parties which we at Picreel have screened and are found qualified and reliable virtual assistants who help us in the service we offer in our website in giving support and assistance to you, our clients, and who have agreed to treat your personal information confidential. Disclosure is applied when it is deemed necessary especially in compliance with the rules of the law, in the implementation of the site’s policy and of for the protection of the rights of our company’s and of our clients’ property and/or safety. In some cases, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be disclosed to other parties for marketing and/or advertising purposes.Certain products and/or services are offered in our site at some occasions, and in this case, other companies have their own independent privacy policies which are applied in which we have no responsibility.

Policy Toward Children

In compliance with the Children Online Privacy Protection Act or COPPA any personal information from 13 years old individuals and below are not collected nor stored. We also proclaim that our products and/or services are for ages 13 years and above. 

Refund Policy

A refund will be imposed within 30 days if you, our clients are not 100% satisfied.

Terms and Conditions

Kindly visit our Terms and Conditions tab which establishes the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms Of Service

Agreement

By using Picreel, you agreed to be covered by our privacy policy. 

Changes of Privacy Policy

Picreel retains the right to change its privacy policy, however, changes will be posted on this page, if any, for user’s information.  
Last modified: October, 2013  
Questions and suggestions:For inquiries, suggestions and requests, you may reach us at contact@picreel.com or visit
